export const initialStateItemsTime = [
    {
      question: 'Time: Shall we go to the cinema ... Sunday?',
      answer: 'on',
    }, {
      question: 'Time: He graduated from Oxford ... 1985.',
      answer: 'in',
    }, { 
      question: 'Time: I must get up early ... the morning.',
      answer: 'in',
    }, {
      question: 'Time:The shops open ... nine.',
      answer: 'at',
  }, 
  //TODO wyłączyć komentarze {
    //   question: 'Time:She has never seen the sea ... winter.',
    //   answer: 'in',
    // }, {
    //   question: 'Time:I am going to meet her ... Wednesday.',
    //   answer: 'on',
    // },
]

export const initialStateItemsPlace = [
    {
      question: 'Place: Shall we go to the cinema ... Sunday?',
      answer: 'on',
    }, {
      question: 'Place: He graduated from Oxford ... 1985.',
      answer: 'in',
    }, {
      question: 'Place: I must get up early ... the morning.',
      answer: 'in',
    }, {
      question: 'Place:The shops open ... nine.',
      answer: 'at',
    }, {
      question: 'Place:She has never seen the sea ... winter.',
      answer: 'in',
    }, {
      question: 'Place:I am going to meet her ... Wednesday.',
      answer: 'on',
    },
]
  